magnetstreet.com 2017-10-08

# Privacy Policy

### MagnetStreet’s Commitment To Your Privacy.

To better protect your privacy, MagnetStreet provides this Privacy Policy ("Policy") explaining its online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This Policy applies to all of the products and services offered through MagnetStreet.com ("Website"). If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us through this Website, or write to us at:   
MagnetStreet  
285 West Loop Road  
Wheaton IL 60189  
Attention: Privacy Officer.

MagnetStreet adheres to strict privacy principles with respect to the data collection practices on this Website, and complies with the Federal Trade Commission guidelines and all applicable U.S. federal and state laws and regulations. 

#### Notice.

MagnetStreet is committed to clearly and readily disclosing its data collection practices so that you can make informed decisions about your activities on this Website. 

#### Choice.

MagnetStreet provides you with a choice to participate in its data collection activities either anonymously or not at all. 

#### Access.

MagnetStreet provides you with the opportunity to review, modify, and delete any personally identifiable information that you have previously provided. 

#### Security

MagnetStreet has taken proactive measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of data that it collects and stores. MagnetStreet's network infrastructure utilizes leading technology, including Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software which encrypts information, to protect data at each point of transfer. MagnetStreet uses multiple back-up systems to reduce the chance of data loss and for up-to-date and accurate information. MagnetStreet utilizes up-todate physical security procedures to limit access to the data so that any access is consistent with this Policy. MagnetStreet transmits your entire credit card number to Authorize.Net during order processing. 

#### Information Collected.

In order to provide you with the full range of products and services available through this Website, MagnetStreet may collect the following types of information: 

  * #### Information You Provide.

When you make a purchase, sign up for any MagnetStreet services, or submit a request for information or assistance, you will be asked to submit personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, or telephone number, and, where relevant, payment information, through MagnetStreet's secure online order form. 

  * #### Payment Information.

MagnetStreet will never share your payment instrument information with any person other than as necessary to process the payments you authorize. MagnetStreet does not store your payment instrument information on MagnetStreet's servers. Rather, we partner with Braintree Payment Services (“Braintree”), a globally respected payment gateway, to leverage its secure vault solutions for all payment instrument storage. All data sent to MagnetStreet’s servers is encrypted and our servers are protected by industry standard measures. By leveraging Braintree for storage, we are able to add another powerful layer of security to MagnetStreet. 

  * #### Cookies.

When you visit this Website, MagnetStreet may send one or more cookies, a small file containing a string of characters, to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. MagnetStreet uses cookies to improve the quality of this Website by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Some of this Website’s features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on user's prior visits to this website. 

We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, click here 

  * #### User Communications.

When you send an email or other communication to MagnetStreet through this Website or otherwise, MagnetStreet may retain those communications, and the personally identifiable information you provide for a response in order to fulfill your order, process your inquiry, respond to your request, and to improve this Website and MagnetStreet's products and services. MagnetStreet will not use return email addresses for any other purpose unless you agree to that use.

  * #### Affiliated Web Sites.

MagnetStreet may offer products and services in connection with third-party websites. Personally identifiable information that you provide to third-party websites may be sent to MagnetStreet. MagnetStreet processes such personally identifiable information in accordance with this Policy. The third-party websites may have different privacy practices and you should read their privacy policies.

  * #### Links.

MagnetStreet may present links in a format that tracks whether these links have been followed. This information is used internally to improve the quality of MagnetStreet's products, services, and this Website by tracking user trends. 

  * #### Third-Party Web Sites.

This Policy only applies to this Website and any other website owned and operated by MagnetStreet. Please be aware that MagnetStreet is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other websites and does not exercise control over third-party websites displayed as links anywhere on this Website. These third-party websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information from you. In certain instances, if you affirmatively click through to access sponsored content or materials at sponsored websites, or affirmatively click through on a link/ad, that user's information may be shared with the sponsor. 

  * #### Advertising.

Third party vendors, including Google, show MagnetStreet's ads on sites on the internet. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Alternatively users may opt out of third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Third party vendors may collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. Users may opt out of third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the   
[Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

#### How MagnetStreet Uses Your Information.

When MagnetStreet has co-branded, customized, private label, or sponsored products and services, or joins with other parties to provide specific products or services, then MagnetStreet may share (provide and receive) your personally identifiable information with those other parties. These third parties will use your personally identifiable information according to their own privacy policies. 

You will occasionally receive emails containing information on products, services, special offers, contests, promotions or a newsletter. MagnetStreet provides you with a mechanism to opt-out from receiving these types of communications. To unsubscribe, please send an email to [unsubscribe@magnetstreet.com](mailto:unsubscribe@magnetstreet.com). 

MagnetStreet may disclose certain of your personally identifiable information to third-party service providers in order to fulfill your order. These third-party service providers have agreed to use your personally identifiable information only to fulfill your order and to keep it secure and confidential. MagnetStreet may share aggregate information, such as usage and demographic data, with third parties. Aggregate information does not include personally identifiable information. 

MagnetStreet is the sole owner of all information collected on this Website. MagnetStreet will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third parties, except as set forth in this Policy.

MagnetStreet reserves the right to disclose any information collected at this Website if required by law or valid order of a court or other governmental authority. 

#### Update, Correct, Delete, Deactivate and/or Access Your Personal Information.

Upon request, MagnetStreet will grant individuals reasonable access to the personally identifiable information that it holds about them. If your personally identifiable information changes (such as Zip Code, phone, email, or postal address), or if you wish to have your information removed from MagnetStreet's database, you may contact MagnetStreet by emailing MagnetStreet's Customer Department at [info@magnetstreet.com](mailto:info@magnetstreet.com) or by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

To protect your privacy and security, MagnetStreet will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

#### Your California Privacy Rights. 

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits those customers that are California residents to request information about how MagnetStreet discloses certain categories of personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. California residents may also request that MagnetStreet not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing use. Except as set out in this Policy, MagnetStreet does not presently share personally identifiable information with any third parties. 

#### Notice of Changes   
To This Policy.

If MagnetStreet modifies this Policy, the changes will be posted on this Website. You should check this Policy regularly to keep abreast of any changes. If MagnetStreet decides to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in this Policy at the time of collection, MagnetStreet will notify you via email and by posting a notice on this Website for thirty (30) days before implementing such changes. 

#### Contact Information.

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding this Policy, please contact MagnetStreet at:  
Phone: 800-788-8633  
Fax: (763) 786-9393  
Email: [info@magnetstreet.com](mailto:info@magnetstreet.com)  
Postal Address: 285 West Loop Road, Wheaton IL 60189  
Web site URL: www.MagnetStreet.com

EFFECTIVE DATE   
October 15, 2008  
1663342v1/12755-0001
